yes yes a big one with the Mother of God
да да большую с Богоматерь
if there is also a small one I just don't
если там ещё маленькая я просто
see a small one take one too let's
маленькую не вижу ещё маленькую возьмите
see op it fell even
посмотрим оп она упала даже
all this is a bad
всё это плохой
sign
знак
Hello Hello I am from the city of
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте я из города
Khmelnitsky where are you from
Хмельницкий Вы откуда
Russia Moscow I understand what profession
Россия Москва Поня кто по профессии
you are an electrician I understand I see you have an
вы электромонтажник понял я вижу у вас
icon I am just an icon painter did you
икона Я просто иконописец это вы где-то
buy it somewhere in a church or in a
покупали в церкви или так в
store
магазине
honestly I am at a summer cottage it was my mother-in-law who
честно я нахожусь на дачном участке это
bought it a summer cottage to
покупала дача
answer this question I understood just well the
т ответить на этот вопрос понял просто
icon needs to be consecrated The
ну нужно чтобы икона была освященная
thing is that For example when I paint icons also if the priest doesn't consecrate them they can't be hung at home Well you understand that the icon then doesn't work I think that the mother-in-law is such a person well she just won't do it Well it seems so The thing is that there are a lot of women
Дело в том что очень много вот женщин
who go Here are a hundred older people
которые ходят Вот ста старшего возраста
in church they just see
в церкви они просто где-то видят
some icon somewhere buy it at the market they can palm
какую-то икону покупают на базаре могут
off an icon Can you show me Well this is
впарить икону А можете показать Ну это
well or is it canonical can you take it off me
ну или она каноническая можете мне её
I want to see from my
снять Я хочу посмотреть у меня с
professional point of view Interesting
профессиональной точки зрения Интересно
and  what kind of big or yes yes big
а какую именно большую или да да большую
with the Mother of God
с Богоматерь
if there is also a small one I just don't
если там ещё маленькая я просто
see a small one take it too let's
маленькую не вижу ещё маленькую возьмите
see op it fell It's a
посмотрим оп она упала
bad
Это плохой
sign It's a bad sign it didn't
знак Это плохой
break what is it Yes I'm
разбилось что
in writing I see the signature is written
она Да я письменна смотрю подпись написа
And you raise it higher Yes the
А вы выше
font is a little wrong Well it's obvious the amateur didn't
Да шрифт немного не тот Ну видно аматор
write this but the second icon
писал не это так а вторую икону
Show me Oh
Покажите
this
О это
[music]
[музыка]
six-meter word
шестиметровой словом
well so she has three swords on one
ну так у неё у неё три меча с одной
side and three on the other What does it have to do with the
стороны и три с другой Причём тут в
family that everything was
семье что было всё
fine this is how I understood and there is
нормально это вот так вот понял а там
also below One one sword see the seventh yes yes come on
ещё снизу Одна один меч видите седьмой
Decipher no no I just well this is a
да да ну-ка Расшифруйте нене Я просто ну
week you know what it is No well well this is
это седмица знаете что
just a very
такое Нет ну вот ну это просто очень
long story you need a seminary okay
долго рассказывать нужно семинарию ладно
Well thank you for now I'm
Ну спасибо что пока мне интересно
really interested because in different
действительно потому что вот в разных
regions there are different icons And by the way, how do you feel about
регионах разные иконы А вы кстати к
politics because
политике как относитесь потому что меня
somehow the Russians are all starting to ask me
что-то россияне Все начинают спрашивать
whose Crimea whose Crimea because of the flag
чей Крым чей Крым из-за флага
eh honestly honestly
э честно честно
eh I've already come from my own
э Я со свого уже
I've already been there and
пришёл Я уже там побывал
I
а и я
understood in short
понял короче
I well this In short this is all
я ну это Короче это это всё
this is not yours Not ours I I don't know how to
это это не ваш Не наш я я не знаю как
explain it simply And how did you get to
просто это объяснить А как ты попал на
yours like you were a contract soldier a volunteer
сво типа ты контрактник был доброволец
who mobilization mobilization And how did they
кто мобилизация мобилизация А как же
let you go from mobilization I saw that they do
тебя отпустили с мобилизации я видел что
n't let out mobilizations yet Zro or
там не отпускают ещё мобили Зро или
earlier earlier earlier and what
ранее ране ранее а что что
happened look Well
случилось смотри Ну
show me Cool Well what is this a
покажи Прикольно А ну что это
fragment flew in And in what direction were there
прилетело осколок А на каком направлении
a lot of fragments a wound in the skull
это было много осколков ранение в череп
there well well it
там
was possible that maybe I
ну ну была возможно то что может быть и
won't survive But in addition to the head there were also some in the
не выживу Но помимо головы там ещё и в
legs
ноги
Well there from all
прилете Ну там со всех
sides the direction was Kharkov Kherson
сторон направление было Харьков Херсон
Where is this uh this is a
Где это э
job job got it This is a
Ээ это работино работино понял Это
counteroffensive so they stepped on you yes it turns
контрнаступ так на вас наступили да
out Well listen But it was somewhere
получается Ну слушай Но это было где-то
T 3-4 months ago Yes you
Т 3-4 месяца назад назад Да это вы
tried to fight back yes like A this is true
пробовали отбивать да типа А это правда
look the truth they say Well I just don't
смотри правда говорят Ну я просто не
know Well I've seen in these things more than once that like
знаю Ну я в этих вещах не раз что типа
ours show that Russians are
наши показывают что вот россиян пускают
just let in crowds like for meat assaults like to
просто толпами как на мясные штурмы типа
press no no there is no such thing There is you know how
жать нет нет такого нету Есть знаешь как
I'll tell you so there is a
я тебе так
base let's say in  Crimea for
скажу есть база допустим в Крыму к
example let's
примеру вот
say I don't know Well I hope they don't
допустим я не знаю Ну надеюсь нас не
register us there so that they won't accept us later there is a
записывают там чтобы нас потом не
base in Crimea
приняли есть допустим база в Крыму в
let's say there are 6000 people there in Crimea and
Крыму допустим есть там 6000 человек а
they are
они с Крыма
redeploying from Crimea Let's say Well I for
перебазировки Ну допустим Ну я к
example there is a transfer back everyone who is
примеру обратно идёт переброска все кто
still alive goes back and again and that's it,
остался живые идёт обратно и опять и вот
well, like a cycle like that goes that
такая вот ну как бы круговорот вот такой
is from Crimea to Zaporozhye from
вот идт то есть из Крыма в Запорожье из
Crimea to Zaporozhye that is there is no such thing
Крыма в Запорожье то есть нет такого то
that there is constantly going on
что там постоянно идёт
there are your guys with whom you are
там вот твоих ребят с которыми тебя
mobile Zro You know there Well how many
мобили Зро Ты там знаешь Ну сколько
died how many are alive Or you don't communicate with them
погибло сколько живых Или ты с ними не
sleep
общаешься сно
60 leave that was leaving with me
уходит 60 вот вместе со мной уходило
60 well somewhere around 30 people are
60 ну где-то человек 30 обратно
returning That is not half for going out Yes it's
возвращается То есть за выход половины
crazy that you were still lucky
Да жесть то тебе ещё фартануло
Well something like that Something like that it's
получается Ну типа того Типа
me it They carried me out
того это меня это Меня вынесли ещё
and well, like an evacuation there well, like in
и ну как бы эвакуация там ну как бы в
this regard the Armed Forces are fine there in terms of
этом плане ВС нормально там в плане
evacuation in
эвакуации в
terms And what about the state Now it
плане А что вот государство Теперь оно
turns out it forgot about you like well it
про тебя получается забыло типа ну всё
took everything away and like you are no longer needed by the state
отвез и типа ты уже не нужен государству
that's it No  Well, they paid the money There,
так получается Не ну денег выплатили Там
as it were, and how much, how many
как бы а сколько сколько
people are paid, my neighbor, he's no longer
платт человек у меня соседа его уже нету
there, he brought only his legs, they
там одни ноги привезли
paid 8
выплатили рублям 8
million rubles And as a war veteran, they pay me
млн А мне как ветерану войны выплачивают
38,000 rubles every month and they paid another
38.000 руб каждый месяц и выплатили ещё
4 million rubles That is, they pay you 380
4 млн руб То есть тебе платят 380
dollars, like a disability pension, yes It
долларов типа пенсию по инвалидности да
turns out, like a veteran, yes So listen, well,
Получается как ветерану да Так слушай ну
I don't know Well, 4 liters of rubles is 40 dollars,
я не знаю Ну 4 л руб - это 40 долларов
yes, I
да
remained disabled there, it
остался там инвалидом
turns out, due to mobilization, I went I was
получается по мобилизации пошл я был
just a driver, I was a driver,
просто я просто водителем был я водителе
and what did you
а что
carry,
возил
fuel, lubricants,
ГСМ
burning
горю смазочный
lubricants How do you think that you helped
материал Как ты считаешь что ты помогал
Ukrainians, even though you drive Well,
украинцев хоть ты же водите
I never killed anyone Well, how did I not
Ну я никого не убил ни разу Ну как не
kill Look, you were delivering flammable
убил Смотри ты подвозил горючие
materials with which you refueled what was
материалы с помощью которых заправляла
killing
то что убивало
Ukrainians Listen, well, well, probably yes,
украинцев Слушай ну ну наверное да
probably yes, this is my, like, if I
наверное да это моя как бы если я так
did it like that, probably yes But how do you Do you
делал наверное да А вот ты как Ты
regret it or not, a
жалеешь об этом или не жалеешь
difficult question I like difficult
сложный вопрос Я люблю сложные
questions, I find it difficult to answer ok And
вопросы затрудняюсь ответить хорошо А
look, how do you think who  guilty that
смотри как ты считаешь кто виноват в том
you were taken to their place And that you are wounded
что тебя забрали на сво И что ты ранен
now Well, I think that the mobilization
теперь Ну я считаю то что мобилизация
took place
прошла
Well, as if Putin is clear by
Ну как бы Путин понятно по
signing the
подписал
mobilization Well, that is, it turns out that
мобилизацию Ну то есть получается ну
Putin is guilty of starting this war and
Путин виноват что эту войну развязал и
throwing you, like, to be slaughtered in
кидает вас типа на убой в
Ukraine Well, the point here is not that he
Украину Да тут дело-то не в том что
started it there Well, can I hang it back Yes, they hung it up, hang it up
развязал там ну можно я повешу обратно
Listen, I probably wont be able to reach it to hang it up Yes, we
Слушай а я наверное не дотянусь чтобы
need to hang two icons so that there would be
Да надо повешать две икону чтобы было
canons,
канони
I
я
understand
понял
Opa This is a bad
Опа Это плохой
sign, the second time the icon falls, the same
знак второй раз икона падает та же
one, we need to hang it up Because if it
самая нужно её повесить Потому что если
falls for the third time, it will simply be This You
третий раз упадёт это будет просто
think thats it, well, the sign is very bad,
Это Думаешь уже всё ну знак очень плохой
its some kind of hanging, you see, the
это какой-то висит видно на тебе видишь
icon is
икона
reacting Listen, its just that a tall
реагирует Слушай просто ну вешал высокий
man was hanging it up and Im already, well, I just dont Well, look, we
человек а я уже ну просто не Ну смотри
need to hang it up because we need to come up with something
нужно повесить потому что что-то нужно
because you see, this is a
придумать потому что видишь это знак
bad sign, but we need to hang it up Ill reach, hang it up, youll reach Well,
плохой но нужно повесить её
God will
Я дотянусь повесить дотянешься Ну Бог
help Lets do this second one now, but be
поможет Давай теперь эту вторую но так
careful so that the icon doesnt fall, I
аккуратно чтобы не упала
understand Well,
икона я понял
we need to put it back in its place,
Ну мы должны вернуть на место её
not  I
не
'm pulling Maybe the
натягиваю Может
stand just pull it out
подставочный вытяни
harder Try like throwing it
э сильнее Попробуй так типа подкинуть
up and like that, well, hook it like jump a
кверху её и так ну зацепить так типа
little I
чуть-чуть прыгнуть
can of course try Let's go to this
Могу конечно попробовать Давай на этот
table Yes, this is not a table, this is a sofa Well, on the
столик Да это не столик это диван Ну на
sofa Yes, so
диван
that it doesn't come apart, don't separate
Да чтоб не разъехался не разъединять
it, everything is untied,
ло всё
untied This is bad It needs to be
развязался развязалась Это плохо Нужно
tied God, what have we done
завязать Боже что мы натворили
Why are things like this Well, I'm telling you, this thing is not a
Зачем так дела Ну я же говорю это вещ не
canonical icon, some amateurs
каноническая икона какие-то аматоры
did not do the hook,
делали не сделали зацеп
no It seems like there are no
не Она походу не
corrections, she, she, look, because
поправления она она смотри потому что
she'll fall I see that the top is coming off, her
она упадёт я вижу она верхушка отходит у
top is coming off, no And there's a
неё верхушка отходит не А там так
fastener there Well, because of this, she'll
крепёж Ну так она сейчас из-за этого
fall now, well, she pressed it close to this,
упадёт ну придавила близко к этому была
because I'll bang the doors a little somewhere
потому что не немного где-то стукну
and it will fall off and this will be Well, if it
дверьми и она отвалится и это будет Ну
falls for the third time, this will be just really
третий раз упадёт это будет просто очень
bad,
плохо
knock our [music
нуть наши
] the
[музыка]
sorcerer's
вороже
sun for the
сонце за
bottom at his [music
пону у сво
] side
[музыка]
we'll
сторо мы
put
положим
[music]
[музыка]
for we'll
за
show
покажем
attached Well, look okay, can you
прицепил Ну смотри нормально а можешь
bring the camera closer because well, I
камеру ближе поднести потому что ну я
can't see well or is it okay there Yes, it
плохо вижу или она нормально там Да
seems okay Well,
вроде
just don't shake
нормально Ну только не тряси
the camera, it's hanging unevenly Well, how
камерой так она неровно висит Ну как
unevenly Well, unevenly Well, maybe you have
неровно Ну неровно Ну может у тебя
a little, well, vision correction after an
немножко ну коррекция зрения после
injury, but it's hanging a little crooked,
ранения но она немножко криво висит
correct it, it fell for the third
поправ она упала третий
time, the third time
раз третий раз
Oh my, the third
ё-моё третий
time Wait, take it all, lift it up You
раз Подожди всё возьми Её
can't hang it up
подними нельзя её вешать
now I understand You need to, you need to pray for it, show it didn't break, show it there's no
сейчас я понял Надо надо отмолить
fracture, no,
покажи она не разбилась покажи разлома
it didn't develop, yes, but it flew
нет нет она не развилась да да но но
off, the frame flew apart Yes, the frame
отлетела рамка разлетелась Да рамка
flew apart Take it all, don't hang it up,
разлетелась возьми Её всё не вешай
take it in your hands You need a prayer here,
возьми Её в руки тут нужна молитва
just damn it, I understood this is a prayer, you need it
сейчас просто блин я понял это молитву
so that it doesn't need a prayer Oh,
нужно чтоб не было нужно молитву Ой
God, do you think everything is so serious, yes,
Боже ты думаешь так всё серьёзно да да
well, if it fell twice, I thought it fell three times
ну если два раза я ещё подумал три раза
But that was me when I was
упало Но это я когда в семинарии
studying at the theological seminary Well, they told us if an
духовной учился Ну нам рассказывали если
icon or the Bible falls three times, it's a
три раза падает икона либо Библия это
very bad sign, it could be death, you
очень плохой знак это может быть смерть
need to pray for it very
нужно отмолить очень
quickly Sit down Sit down with this  icons Let's
быстро Сядь Сядь с этой иконы Давай
pray now Well
сейчас помолимся
maybe
так Ну может
just don't hang it That's all don't hang it already
просто не вешай Всё ты её не вешай уже
Take it in your hands Take it in your
сейчас возьми Её в руки возьми Её в
hands fly That's
руки муха Вот это
brutal Yeah I've only seen this a couple of times in my
жесть Угу я я такое пару раз только в
life when an icon falls Take it
жизни видел чтобы икона падала возьми Её
in your
в
hands Take it Well so that I could see it Let's
руки взял Ну чтобы я её видел Давай
pray
помолимся
and say Mother of God Virgin Mother of
да скажи Богородица
God Virgin of the Seven Arrows
Дева Богородица Дева Семистрельная
Forgive me a sinner
Семистрельная прости меня грешника
Forgive me a sinner Something in life is
прости меня грешника что-то в жизни не
wrong I
так я
did Something in life is wrong I did A
сделал что-то в жизни не так я сделал
mortal sin took on the soul
грех смертный на душу взял
Probably a Greek took death on the soul
наверное грек смер на душ взял
Probably Kaya is
наверное Каю
strong Kaya is strong for those killed in
сильная Каю сильная за убиенных в
Ukraine For those killed in Ukraine For children
Украине за убиенных в Украине за детей
adults For children adults I ask little for
взрослых за детей взрослых прошу малю о
mercy I ask little for mercy Don't reproach me and
пощаде прошу о пощаде не корай меня и
my family Don't reproach me and
род мой не корай меня и и род
my family The rulers who sent me
мой властителей которые послали меня
there The rulers who sent me
туда властителей которые послали меня
there Let it
туда Пусть на них
go against them They go against them They started this
перейдёт Они перет они развязали эту
war They started a
войну Они развязали
war The ambassador
войну посла войска в
sent troops to Ukraine to Ukraine Let them accept
Украину послали во Украину Пусть примут
They what what  let them accept instead of me let them
Они что что пусть примут они вместо меня
accept not instead of me until
пусть пусть примут не вместо меня до 4
May 4th on Easter Sunday Christ
мая на Пасху на воскресенье
rose on Easter May USA has already That's good come on
воскрес США уже Это уже хорошо давай
come on without a name Yes let the one who
давай без имени Да пусть пусть тот кто
sends
посылает на войну
people to war Let only send people to war
людей Пусть токто посылает на войну
himself My word is
сам слово моё
strong My word is strong and three times Amen
крепко слово моё крепко и трижды Аминь
say Amen Amen Amen that's all Look don't hang
скажи Аминь Аминь Аминь всё Смотри не
this
вешай сегодня эту
candle at home today there is a
свечка дома
post put a candle Let today
есть поста поставь свечу Пусть сегодня
preferably and the ass let it
желательно и зад пусть она максимум
burn for a long time at most so big so that the replacement of
погорилая такой большой то чтобы замена
candles
свечей
was relatives better not to tell that the
была родственникам лучше не говорить что
icon fell because the mother-in-law Maybe she is
падала икона потому что тёща Может она
very if she is a believer she can well let's
очень если верующая у неё может ну
say have an attack because of this that well
скажем приступ быть из-за этого что ну
she understands what it is the icon fell three times it
она понимает что такое трижды упала
is better not to burn it after all the woman
лучше её не мировать всё-таки женщина
you know the eldest How
знаете старшая Сколько ей
old is she damn how old is
лет блин сколько
she sixty-sixth year Well yes like
она шестьдесят шестого года Ну да типа
old And is there a candle now you can now
старая А есть свеча сейчас можешь сейчас
press it better Well so that there is none well if there is none
зажать лучше Ну чтобы нету ну если нету
If there is no candle then for example on the gas stove
Если нет Свечи то например на плите газ
so that there is a fire for 12 hours there should
чтобы был огонь 12 часов должен какой-то
be some kind of fire too that
огонь быть тоже
is  since ancient times there was also that like this they
есть издревле ещ было что вот как огнём
carried out with fire They carried out purification with fire and water
проводили Огнём и водой проводили
The thing is that Well it fell three times I did
очищение Дело в том что Ну три раза
n't think that this could be
упало я я не думал что такое может быть
but it is very visible something terrible Well I do
но это видно очень что-то страшное Ну я
n't know
не знаю
Maybe people who were in Ukraine
Может людей которые были уены в Украине
Maybe they Well they can travel
Может они Ну они ж могут путешествовать
they can't and
они не могут
their home has no borders for them you understand the
ивой дом для них нету границ понимаешь
SBU won't come for example or Budanov
там СБУ не приедет например или Буданов
may not come across the border and then they
может не приехать через границу и то
come yes Or he flies in and they they
приезжают да Или прилетает а они они
can always come and moreover they can
могут прийти всегда и причём могут
come you have children
прийти у тебя дети
of course
есть конечно
how many
сколько
two How
двое Сколько
old 7 and 1 7 and 1 damn That is there are
лет 7 и1 7 и1 блин То есть
minors yes they can
несовершеннолетние есть да на них может
still The thing is that minor
ещё Дело в том что несовершеннолетние
children They especially if you have boys
дети Они особенно если мальчики у тебя
boys or girls
мальчики или девочки
boy and girl here on the boy Maybe it is
мальчик и девочка вот на мальчика Может
the father's Maybe it can pass to the son
именно отцовский Может на сына перейти
here was something like this in the Bible If you remember
вот было такое в Библии Если помнишь
the Gospel of
Евангелие от
andrologist
андролог
Simeon you don't remember this well I didn't read it I
симеона не помнишь это ну не читал Я так
understood you don't
понял ты Библию не
actually read the Bible When I was
читаешь на самом деле Когда я был
little
маленький
I read all this but now I don't remember not
Я всё это читал но сейчас не помню не
by I
по Я
read  Bible schools went There was such There was
читал библейские школы ходил Было такое
yes Well somewhere you see didn't get it you
Было было да Ну где-то видишь не доходил
need Yes the thing is that now this
нужно Да дело в том что сейчас вот это
now very much in churches there are priests these
сейчас очень много в церквях есть попы
rich people
вот эти богачи
they are
они есть
normal very much about in a cassock because it was
нормаль оче много об в рясу потому было
said in the scripture that before the arrival so he will
в писании сказано что перед приходом так
come in the form of a priest he will be
придёт в образе священника он будет
Leslie in words he will say that
Лесли вый на слова он будет говорить что
war is peace war is a blessing and
война - Это мир война - это благо и
sending people to war And you this
посылать людей на войну И вас вот этот
same Kirill Patriarch now he really
же сейчас Кирилл патриарх он реально
supports the fact that people like
мобили Зро поддерживает то чтобы вот
you mobile Zro they are sent to
таких как ты мобили Зро их отправляли на
war it is very scary very scary
войну это очень страшно очень страшно
he Patriarch Kirill he is already so it is
он Патриарх Кирилл он уже бо так это
unambiguous but the problem is that they
однозначно но проблема в том что они
want to leave taking the more people from
хотят уйти забрав чем больше людей из
Russia These are the kind of ordinary people as you
России Вот таких простых людей как ты
understand they do throw a sin on you
понимаешь они делают накидывать на вас
So you need
грех Значит нужно
uh 12 hours for
ээ 12 часов чтобы был
this Candle to be and 40
этот Свеча и 40
days once a day you need to pray that the
дней раз в день нужно молиться о том
terrible which you took upon yourself
чтобы страшные который ты взял на себя
on the one who sent you to war that is
на того кто тебя отправил на войну то
this is also described in the Bible If
есть вот это в Библии тоже описано Если
you see if you if you were  contract
видишь если тебя если бы ты был
soldier that's it And so you mobile Zro
контрактник то такое А так ты мобили Зро
Yes you can
Да ты можешь
this to the one who mobile Zro you that is
этот тому кто тебя мобили Зро то есть
Putin that's why I had a vision that
Путину поэтому у меня было ведение что
he will be on Christ's Sunday until May 4
он до 4 мая на воскресенье
And so it is necessary that all those
христову И вот нужно чтобы
killed by him and also all those who
всех убиенных ним и также все кто на
help themselves in Ukraine pray for
себя помогая людей в Украине молились о
this and
это и его
take him will take him he will
забрал заберёт его он с 4
not remain from him from May 4
мая не останется от него
such at I don't
такое
know somehow it's
знаю как-то это
so too confident Yes I
так слишком уверенно Да
got it And your mother-in-law she lives in what city
понял А твоя тёща она в каком городе
with us in Moscow in Moscow yes I
живёт вме с нами в Москве в Москве да
got it Muscovites Yes and how she
понял москвичи Да а как она вот
worried about you in
переживала за тебя в
her Listen yes in fact now I have
сво Слушай да на самом деле сейчас у
that is
меня то есть
not me on my
не я по моей
side brother In short mine still he
линии братишка Короче мой ещё он по
went under contract Well not my Bra but
контракту пошёл Ну не мой Бра а
my
двоюродный брат моей
wife's cousin here he is now he is still
жены вот он вот он сейчас до сих пор
there I think it's an icon that's why it fell that
там я думаю это икона поэтому и упала то
is maybe he has
есть возможно он завтра
already fallen three times tomorrow the icon tomorrow brother
уже трижды упала икона завтра братишка
Listen
Слушай
well he said that he would accept standing Well standing
ну он сказал что примет стоя Ну вот стоя
Lesha it
Лёша
doesn't matter Well that's it the icon fell three times I
неважно Ну всё икона ри трижды упала Я
think  what is he there by the way in the
думаю что ему там там кстати на
Zaporizhzhya direction there are a lot of
запорожском направлении очень много
Ukrainian drones I think he will be
украинских Дронов Я думаю он будет
standing he has a
стоять
vision right now I see he is
ему видение у меня прямо сейчас вижу он
standing he is trying to brush it off with his hand this
стоит он пробует его смахнуть рукой этот
drone And this drone to him
Дрон А этот Дрон ему
And from above with a mavic the Ukrainians are filming a video
И сверху мавиком украинцы снимают видео
cool and then they are watching on Telegram channels
классненько и потом по Telegram каналах
Oh I sometimes have such a
рассматривают Ой у меня бывает такое
vision it's
видение
brutal we'll see how what we'll
жесть смотрим посмотрим как что
see and how how how how what is my brother's last
посмотрим а как как как как брата
name yes I'll try to
фамилия да я сейчас попробую
look now what is this wife's brother's last name and
заглянуть как этого брата жены фамилия а
Now wait this one's
Сейчас подожди этого зовут так его Саша
name is Sasha his name is so
зовут так
and
а
Sergievsky Sergievsky And by patronymic
Сергиевский Сергиевский А по отчеству
Alexander Sergeevsky Alexander
Александр сергеевский Александр
who is Sergeevich Sergeevsky Alexander
кто а Сергеевич сергеевский Александр
Sergeevich original Yes what year was he
Сергеевич оригинально Да какой год
born so if so now wait
рождения так если так сейчас подожди
if I was born in eighty-fifth
если я восемьдесят пятого
eighty-seventh eighty-seventh year Yes
восемьдесят седьмого восемьдесят
no longer young Yes
седьмого года Да уже не молоденький Да
Sergeevsky Alexander Sergeev born in
сергеевский Александр Сергеев
eighty-seventh year I see I see
восемьдесят седьмого года Вижу
him there
вижу ему там
I
ему я такое
see such a thing really
вижу реально
Drone And if they pay eh or not Or is it
Дрон А если выплачивают э ну или нет Или
only necessary that the body was all there with
только нужно чтобы тело всё было там с
compensation It is desirable that the body was that
компенсацию Желательно чтобы тело было
is the EU  And if there is no head, then what will they
то есть ЕС А если нету головы то что они
pay,
выплатят
well, as proof that this is the body of
ну на доказательство что это именно тело
this person, well, so that the documents were I
этого человека ну чтоб Документы были я
see a very large flint, he is who by the way, there is
вижу Огниво такое очень большое он он
something incomprehensible there, such
кем кстати там что-то непонятное Такое
who is he, he serves there at all, he is an attack aircraft, an attack aircraft, I
кем он он там служит вообще он штурмовик
see ammunition, he sits on the
штурмовик я вижу боекомплект он сидит на
ammunition, the drone flies, he gets up, this is the
боекомплект летит Дрон он встаёт ему это
second drone in the
второй Дрон в
ammunition, such
боекомплект такой
fireworks, smoke
фейерверк дым
passes, no,
проходит нет
but could it be that from the explosion of the
а может быть такое что от взрыва
ammunition there will be nothing left from the body,
боекомплекта не остаться От тела
maybe I see the combat
ничего может я вижу взорвался бой
kit exploded and this Sergievsky is
комплект и этот Сергиевский
just
просто
badaboom I'm like in Telegram, just like
бадабум Я как в телеграме прямо как
twisting this repetition, I see it
перекручивать этот повтор я вижу его
clearly Well, it turns out that he is a
отчётливо Ну а получается Он штурмовик
contract attack aircraft That is, he died deservedly Well, it's his
контрактник То есть он заслуженно погиб
business, yes, it turns out so, yes, I
Да ну по дело ему да получается так да
understood It's cool And what does his wife say,
понял Прикольно А что жена его говорит
she doesn't say that if he dies, they will
она не говорит что если он типа помрёт
pay her
ей выплатят
compensation Well, she doesn't seem to know that
компенсацию Ну Она походу не знает что
she doesn't know that he is an attack aircraft, not that the
она не знает что он штурмовик не что
money
деньги
will be paid Well, she Well, she thinks that what's there
выплатит Ну она Ну она думает то что там
Maybe there is 5,000 there or something else, you are
Может там 5000 там или ещё что-то слу ты
in  normal relations with her communicate
в нормальных отношениях с ней общаетесь
yes call and let her definitely
да позвони и пусть она обязательно
call her husband so that she talks to him
позвонит мужу чтоб Поговорила с ним
because tomorrow he may Well you know better
потому что завтра его может Ну лучше
warn Destiny can be changed better
предупредить Судьбу можно изменить лучше
warn because the vision is very
предупредить потому что ведение очень
clear very clear vision let
отчётливо очень отчётливо ведение пусть
her call him and say that there was a
она позвонит ему и скажет что было
vision he can be changed can be
видение он може можно изменить можно
changed Well even if not changed let
изменить Ну даже если не изменить пусть
her say that she loves him does he have children
она скажет что любит его дети есть у
Yes How old is one one How old is the
него Да Сколько один один Сколько лет
child I will say 12 years 12 years Let the
ребёнку скажу 12 лет 12 лет Пусть
child also call And let her tell
ребёнок тоже позвонит И пусть она скажет
him If anything let him surrender better
ему Если что пусть сдастся в плен лучше
because
потому что
otherwise I see
иначе Вижу
I see such a horror
вижу
that even like they
жесть такая что даже типа
won't pay anything the point of
и не выплатят ничего смысл с этого
all this Well I
всего Ну я тебя
understand you Okay I'll go further then come on come on come on
понял Хорошо пойду дальше тогда
like the comment squeak letter to my Telegram
лайк комент писка пись на мий Telegram
right now axis VN and
прям зараз ось ВН а
pok this is very and very important YouTube is busy with
пок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through scarg or in your ban and very
нас через скарг ор в твый бан и дуже
many videos I don't show to people at times  do not
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams so that
показуе информация про стримы тому для
we Mali operational links are
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
written right now and while there are
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там
okm videos there is also interesting and useful
окм вдео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we are sorry for you
информация и ми повинни з вами тримати
constant operational links
постийний оперативный звязок
independently in order to show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
letter a
пись а